[{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980646576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":11267,"timeElapsed":439302},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980649736,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":3157,"timeElapsed":442462},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980653872,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":4133,"timeElapsed":446598},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980656295,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":2420,"timeElapsed":449021},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980658376,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2076,"timeElapsed":451102},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980662584,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":4205,"timeElapsed":455310},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980667560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":4972,"timeElapsed":460286},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980671568,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":4005,"timeElapsed":464294},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980673887,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":2317,"timeElapsed":466613},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980680031,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5309,"timeElapsed":472757},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980682552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2518,"timeElapsed":475278},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980686184,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3627,"timeElapsed":478910},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980688152,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":1967,"timeElapsed":480878},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980691024,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2870,"timeElapsed":483750},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980693031,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2002,"timeElapsed":485757},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980694527,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1494,"timeElapsed":487253},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980696162,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1632,"timeElapsed":488888},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980698056,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"214","question":"Is there a sound that really bothers you? If so, what is it? If not, has someone ever asked you to stop making a sound because it bothered them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1891,"timeElapsed":490782},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980705367,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":6197,"timeElapsed":498093},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980707425,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2054,"timeElapsed":500151},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980709264,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":1836,"timeElapsed":501990},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980710721,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1455,"timeElapsed":503447},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980712457,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1727,"timeElapsed":505183},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980714896,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2435,"timeElapsed":507622},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980726768,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":11869,"timeElapsed":519494},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980728600,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":1829,"timeElapsed":521326},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980730263,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":1662,"timeElapsed":522989},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980731858,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":1591,"timeElapsed":524584},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980757208,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":24205,"timeElapsed":549934},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980758439,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1229,"timeElapsed":551165},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980760247,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":1806,"timeElapsed":552973},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980761704,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":1454,"timeElapsed":554430},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980762983,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1278,"timeElapsed":555709},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980764376,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":1390,"timeElapsed":557102},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980766560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2181,"timeElapsed":559285},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980768215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":1654,"timeElapsed":560941},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980770360,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2141,"timeElapsed":563086},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980775440,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4414,"timeElapsed":568166},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980776704,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1262,"timeElapsed":569430},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980778648,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":1942,"timeElapsed":571374},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980780079,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":1427,"timeElapsed":572805},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980781320,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1238,"timeElapsed":574046},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980782880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1558,"timeElapsed":575606},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980783919,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1037,"timeElapsed":576645},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980785208,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":1287,"timeElapsed":577934},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980786423,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1213,"timeElapsed":579149},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980793040,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5853,"timeElapsed":585766},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980794456,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":1413,"timeElapsed":587182},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980795815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":1357,"timeElapsed":588541},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980797223,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":1406,"timeElapsed":589949},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980798720,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":1494,"timeElapsed":591446},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980800159,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1438,"timeElapsed":592885},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980801656,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1494,"timeElapsed":594382},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980802913,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":1254,"timeElapsed":595639},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980807608,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4691,"timeElapsed":600333},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980808976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"130","question":"Is there a character from a TV show, movie, or book that you relate to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1366,"timeElapsed":601701},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980812064,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2478,"timeElapsed":604790},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980813951,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":1885,"timeElapsed":606677},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980815528,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1574,"timeElapsed":608254},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980816936,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1405,"timeElapsed":609662},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980818745,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1806,"timeElapsed":611471},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980820471,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":1721,"timeElapsed":613197},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980821792,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":1318,"timeElapsed":614518},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980823368,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":1573,"timeElapsed":616094},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980824745,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":1374,"timeElapsed":617471},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980828215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2701,"timeElapsed":620941},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980829639,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":1422,"timeElapsed":622365},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980831223,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1582,"timeElapsed":623949},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980832552,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1326,"timeElapsed":625278},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980833984,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1430,"timeElapsed":626710},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980835335,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":1349,"timeElapsed":628061},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980836560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":1222,"timeElapsed":629286},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980838320,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":1757,"timeElapsed":631046},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980839799,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"248","question":"When was the last time you went to a museum? What did you see?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":1478,"timeElapsed":632525},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980845377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4614,"timeElapsed":638103},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980846576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":1196,"timeElapsed":639302},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980848151,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":1573,"timeElapsed":640877},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980849463,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1309,"timeElapsed":642189},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980850832,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":1366,"timeElapsed":643558},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980852999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2165,"timeElapsed":645725},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980854625,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1623,"timeElapsed":647351},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980856768,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2140,"timeElapsed":649494},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980857976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":1205,"timeElapsed":650702},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980861456,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2237,"timeElapsed":654182},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980863241,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":1782,"timeElapsed":655967},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980864415,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":1172,"timeElapsed":657141},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980865992,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":1574,"timeElapsed":658718},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980867375,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":1381,"timeElapsed":660101},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980869863,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2485,"timeElapsed":662589},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980873303,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3438,"timeElapsed":666029},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980874672,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":1365,"timeElapsed":667398},{"subjectID":"9ovupvabgl","prolificID":"671e70010b8f04850445045f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2633620b36dfdcb2854","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980876336,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"240","question":"Pick a family member, friend or partner and describe what you think they are currently doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":1660,"timeElapsed":669062}]